Over here!
Here I go!
You're slow!
Line up!
Hmm, what about Sasaki? Is she absent again today?
The tournament is right around the corner.
Hey, Kitamura. Go to the faculty room after practice.
Okay!
Mayhem
You're going home unusually early today
so I thought we should drop by that café last time...
I'm Kitamura Kaori, the female tennis club president.
I'm sorry.
Sasaki Ami, a junior of mine has been
missing our club practice lately.
I'm gonna check up on her at her home.
We barely have time for dates.
I always cause trouble for Masaya-kun,
my childhood friend and lover.
I'm sorry for all of this.
Thank you, Masaya-kun.
W-Well, right...
Be careful, though.
I've been hearing bad rumors about
that second-year student Sasaki-san.
But she's been training in our
tennis club for more than a year.
That's why I believe she will come back to us.
Make sure to keep things smooth.
I know. See you later.
Keep things smooth...
Smooth...
The intercom seems to be ringing. Should we leave it be?
Gosh, right when we're having a nice moment here...
Ugh...
Who's that?
My senior.
Our tennis club president.
No matter what I do, I'm no match for her.
Being around her just makes me feel really miserable.
That's it...
Senpai, I'll hear you out inside if you wanna talk.
Come in first.
Anyways, this one is a fuck buddy.
He's Ryou-kun, a friend of mine.
We're having sex after school.
I don't care about our club anymore.
Hold on, Sasaki-san! Are you out of
your mind? What are you doing!?
Huh?
Your face is beet red, Senpai.
Could it be that you don't have
any experience in this yet?
Huh!?
Hey, Ami... How about having her
join us in a threesome?
No, let me go! Nooo!
Oh, that's a great idea.
Senpai, this guy is very good at it.
Nooooo!
Oh, it's okay. To make it not hurt...
I'll make sure to do stuff like this for you.
Stop! Stop doing this!
Look at your nipples.
They are starting to get harder.
They're so stiff.
Does that mean this one's the same?
Yep, I was right.
You're totally feeling good now.
My body feels limp.
I can't think straight.
I can't fight back!
Whoa... It's so stringy!
Nooooooo!
Whoa, looking good!
I won't be able to hold back any longer!
N-No!
H-Huh!?
I-I don't wanna... I'm begging you!
No, I don't want this!
Masaya-kun, help me!
Oh yeah, Kaori-senpai. Aren't you close to a certain guy?
One look and I can tell he's sort of a late bloomer.
He hasn't put his hands on you yet, just as I expected.
Over here, Senpai. Let's take a photo
to commemorate your defloration.
Huh? You're resisting.
That's not what I wanna see.
A face that says "I'm a slut who loves sex"
is what I'm looking for.
Then how about you use that stuff of yours?
Ah, that's it! Let's do that!
This is my favorite cream.
I'll put some on you as well, Senpai.
What is that...
What is this sensation? Itchy?
Or rather... Hot!?
What is this!? N-Nooo!
I'm scared. I feel an unusual heat
slowly spreading in my body.
I'm scared... I'm scared!
This cream is used to make horses and cows go in heat.
You're kidding me...
She rubbed such a thing on me!?
Wh-What should I do? It was painful up until now...
...but I'm feeling good now.
I can't get enough of this pleasure!
Yes, yes... That face...
An honor student like you
falls from grace and becomes a slave to cocks...
That's what I've been looking for.
How about coming inside her?
For real? Lucky me!
No, absolutely not! Nooo!
It's okay.
Ami got some pills.
It's no use. My body has no strength.
I don't want this.
He forces himself on me,
only to end up coming inside.
I'm begging you...
Anything but inside me...
Oh my, you still have some sense of reason left?
I'll give you more, then.
I'm gonna put lots of it in your asshole as well.
Here it comes... I can feel something crazy...
I'm coming...
Ugh... He said he'd wait an hour more in the park.
Masaya-kun
Sorry, this is gonna take longer. I feel bad for you, Masaya-kun.
Go home without me.
_
We didn't. I think I was able to convince her.
Are you alright? You didn't end up fighting?
_
Great, that's a relief.
I couldn't help worrying earlier.
Don't worry, I'm free for the rest of the day.
I'll wait here for another hour.
Let me know when you're done.
Your boyfriend is slow on the uptake.
Maybe I should tell him to go home already.
No, isn't it the opposite?
Isn't her boyfriend suspicious of you instead?
I mean, look at what you did to her.
Ohh? I see...
In that case, keeping him in the loop here
would prevent any suspicions.
Ah, Kaori...
...and Sasaki-san?
I asked Kaori-senpai
and she told me her boyfriend was waiting for her.
I didn't know and ended up
keeping her this long. I'm sorry.
Kaori... Are you alright? Your face is flushed.
Huh? Ah... Am I?
Ahh, Kaori-senpai. I'll say it.
The truth is my grades sharply dropped
and I'm unable to join our club activities.
But Kaori-senpai said she'd help me study.
So that's what happened...
On this day, Kaori and I basically
stopped going home together.
After her club practice, Sasaki-san would show up
and they'd straight up go to their study group.
To be honest, this makes me feel lonely.
Of course, I'd love to support her.
But today is supposed to be a special day.
Hey, this ointment is almost empty.
We ran through it so fast.
I'm begging you...
Let me go just for today...
Ehh?
It's Masaya-kun's birthday today...
So please...
What a bother.
But well, if that's the case...
Come with me outside for a bit.
If you beat me, our study group will be over today!
No way!
Is that fun?
This is the best! I can't help but laugh here!
They will set me free if I win.
But...
I-I have to wear this thing!
I still feel hot from the drug earlier!
There, too bad for you.
Come on, hang in there!
Huh!?
Show me the willpower of an ace player!
Oh my, I defeated the national-level top ace player.
It sure feels great.
Well then, I won the match.
That means the study group continues.
You can go to your boyfriend now, Senpai.
I am going home
and I'm getting screwed by Ryou-kun's cock with all might.
Please feel free to go, Senpai.
Have a fun talk with your boyfriend or something.
U-Umm...
It feels good!
Wow, this feels amazing...
They won't stop! My hips won't stop!
I've always been with Kaori on my birthdays, though...
Kaori...
I'm sorry, Kaori!
Masaya-kun, I'm sorry!
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji